Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1880-2014 RL.01050
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1946-2014, undated
  - Books, long works, 1957-2012, undated
    - The Promise of Rest, 1993-1996, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1993-1994; 9 folders (Box 117)
      - Notes and drafts, 1994; 7 folders (Box 118)
      - Notes and drafts, 1994 Aug-Oct, undated; 10 folders (Box 119)
        Includes copy-edited and corrected typescripts, and Susan Moldow notes.
      - Notes and drafts, 1994-1995, undated; 5 folders (Box 120)
        Includes An Imminent Curse excerpt; draft of From the Author to the Trade; script for audio abridgement; and, jacket copy and quotes.
      - Proofs, jacket, 1994-1995, undated; 2 folders (Box 120)
      - Proofs, 1994, undated; 2 folders (Box 110)
        Includes sample pages, jacket proofs, and ads.
      - Reviews and Publicity, 1995 Apr 4-1996 Nov 17 (Box 120)
    - The Three Gospels, 1993-1998, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1993 Nov-1994 Dec; 9 folders (Box 120)
        Includes revised typescripts of The Good News According to John; An Apocryphal Gospel; and, Honest Accounts of a Memorable Life.
      - Notes and drafts, 1994 Dec-1995 Oct; 14 folders (Box 121)
        Includes revised typescripts of A Reckless Daring; A New Thing Entirely; A General Preface; The Strangest Story; and, copy edited typescripts.
      - Notes and drafts, 1995, undated; 15 folders (Box 122)
        Includes notes on Hurlbut's Story of the Bible notes and illustrations; revised typescripts of The Strangest Story; Becoming Contemporary with the Gospel Writers; and, flap, forward, and jacket copy.
      - Proofs, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 122)
      - Proofs, cover, undated (Box 110)
      - Proofs, 1995; 2 folders (Box 123)
      - Reviews and Publicity, 1994 Dec-1998 Dec, undated (Box 123)
      - Bookworm interview, 1996 Jun 20; 2 items (Box 291, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0039, RL01050-CS-0058)
      - Notes and drafts, undated; 2 Files 2 MS Word files; 88 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes draft and contents list.
    - The Collected Poems, 1982-1997, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1994-1996, undated; 12 folders (Box 123)
        Includes drafts and revised typescripts of The Collected Poems, including An Actual Temple; The Closing; A Haven; A Long and Sizeable Farewell; preface; and, correspondence with Susan Moldow.
      - Notes and drafts, 1996 Oct, 1997; 6 folders (Box 124)
      - Proofs, 1996 Nov; 3 folders (Box 124)
      - Notes and drafts, 1996-1997, undated; 6 folders (Box 125)
        Includes drafts and revised typescripts of jacket and ad copy; and, The Unaccountable Worth of the World.
      - Notes and drafts, undated; 4 Files 4 MS Word documents; 15 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes drafts of Dream of Teeth; F.H. Again; and, an untitled poem.
      - Proofs, 1982-1986, 1990, 1996-1997; 7 folders (Box 125)
        Includes photocopies of Laws of Ice; The Use of Fire; and, Vital Provisions.
      - Proofs, 1996-1997 (Box 126)
      - Proofs, jacket, undated (Box 110)
      - Reviews, 1997 (Box 123)
    - Roxanna Slade, 1994-2001, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1994, undated; 10 Files 10 rtf files; 1.5 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes a chronology, and unformatted drafts of chapters one through six.
      - Notes and drafts, 1996-1997; 11 folders (Box 126)
      - Notes and drafts, 1997; 9 folders (Box 127)
        Includes revised draft typescripts.
      - Notes and drafts, 1998-1998; 9 folders (Box 128)
      - Notes and drafts, 1998, undated; 3 folders (Box 129)
        Includes chronology notes.
      - Proofs, 1997-1998, undated; 8 folders (Box 129)
        Includes Price's corrections, and cover designs.
      - Proofs, 1997-1998, undated; 3 folders (Box 110)
        Includes jacket, ad, and sample cover.
      - Reviews, 1998 Apr-2001 Oct, undated (Box 129)
      - NC Bookwatch, 1998 May 29 (Box 293, Videotape RL01050-VHS-0014)
    - Learning a Trade, 1955-2000, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1955-1997; 14 folders (Box 130)
        Includes original notebooks and photocopies.
      - Notes and drafts, 1955-1997, undated; 6 folders (Box 131)
        Includes notebook photocopies, and typescript drafts of preface, footnotes, and A Note on the Text.
      - Proofs, 1998; 5 folders (Box 131)
      - Proofs, 1998, undated; 7 folders (Box 132)
      - Proofs, layouts, 1998 (Box 110)
      - Reviews and Publicity, 1998 Mar-2000 Sep (Box 132)
    - A Singular Family, 1998-1999, undated
      - Notes and drafts, typescript addition to preface, 1998 Aug 9 (Box 132)
      - Proofs, 1998-1999; 3 folders (Box 132)
        Includes samples of back cover, and interior design.
      - Proofs, 1999, undated; 3 folders (Box 133)
        Includes page and jacket proofs.
      - Proof, jacket, undated (Box 110)
    - Letter to a Man in the Fire
      - Notes and drafts, 1997 Oct-1998 Aug; 14 folders (Box 133)
        Includes typescripts with Price's revisions; illustrations; notes from Frank Lentricchia
      - Notes and drafts, 1998, undated; 3 folders (Box 134)
      - Proofs, 1998 Nov-Jan 1999, 2000, undated; 9 folders (Box 134)
        Includes Price's corrections; case specifications; and, jacket proofs.
      - Reviews and publicity, 1999 Mar 11 - Dec 5 (Box 134)
    - Feasting the Heart
      - Notes and drafts, 1992, 1995-1998, undated; 19 folders (Box 136)
        Includes notes and revised drafts of flap copy; and essays A Christmas in Rome; Book Tour; The Last Great Weeper; The Ghostwriter in the Cellar; Birthplace; Oral History; Wheelchair Travel; A Single Death Among Many; My Tolerance Problem; The Mad Inventor; The Lucky Child's Christmas; England in the Fifties; Being Reviewed; Crossing Genders; Forty and Counting; and, Summer Vacation.
      - Reading, 1992 Dec 25 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0113)
        Includes an audio recording of Christmas in Rome.
      - Notes and drafts, 1997-2000, undated; 88 Files 88 MS Word and txt files; 957 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes drafts of NPR essays including A Christmas in Rome; A Gallop Down the Homestretch; A Helpful Sight; A lens in the Earth; A Motto; A Perfect Dinner; A Premature Farewell; A School for Husbands; A Shallow Past; A Single Death Among Millions; A Standing Reader; A Weeper; Being Reviewed; Birthplace; Book Tour, 1995; Casting Bread; Christmas at the Core; Crossing Genders; Depression; Dolls in a Man's Life; Eloquent Letters; England in the Fifties; Eyelevel to a Wheelchair; First Words; Forty and Counting; The Gazelle of Israel; The Ghostwriter in the Cellar; Gone With the Wind; The Great Imagination Heist; History; The Home Team; James Dean at 64; Joke-Telling Lessons; The King Tut Show; The Last Great Weeper; Lucky Catches; The Lucky Child's Christmas; The Mad Inventor; MRI Time; My Accent Problem; My Ghost Stories; My Tolerance Problem; Native Orphans; The Old Man in Here with Me; On the Stone; Oral History; Pain; Portable Music; Private Worship; School for Husbands; The Stage, Years Ago; Summer on the Deep; Summer Vacation; Teachers; Teaching Writing; Time-Ridden; Various Parents; What My Parents Didn't Tell Me; Wheelchair Travel; With Ida; and, Worship. Other files include drafts of related correspondence, the table of contents, Price's biography, and lists of broadcast and publication dates.
      - Notes and drafts, 2000; 4 folders (Box 135)
        Includes copyedited typescripts.
      - Proofs, 2000 May-Jun; 6 folders (Box 135)
      - Proofs, 2000 May-Jul; 10 folders (Box 136)
        Includes Price's corrections; sample pages for essay titles; and, cover specifications and samples.
      - Proofs, 2000 Jul (Box 304)
        Includes Anderson's notes.
      - Reviews and Publicity, 2000 (Box 168)
        Includes a poster with excerpt from The Great Imagination Heist in Feasting the Heart: Fifty-two Commentaries for the Air.
      - Reviews and publicity, undated (Box 136)
      - Recordings, 2001; 20 Files 20 wav and mp3 files; 431 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes NPR audio clips of Forty and Counting; A Single Death Among Many; The Commonest Demon; My Tolerance Problem; MRI Time; Private Worship; Lucky Catches; Outside class the question I hear most often is can writing be taught; What My Parents Didn't Tell Me; and, Casting Bread.
    - A Perfect Friend, 1999-2009, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1999-2000; 11 folders (Box 137)
        Includes typescripts with Price's revisions; Erik Larson's notes; A Boy and His Elephant; cover sketches; and, catalog copy.
      - Proofs, 2000, 2002, undated; 5 folders (Box 137)
        Includes sample pages; corrected blue pages; jacket; illustration; and, sample case for hardback.
      - Reviews, 2000 Jun 9-2002 Aug 6, undated (Box 137)
      - Pine View School, 2009 (Box 307)
        Students' response to Price's book, A Perfect Friend.
      - Proofs, jacket, 2000, undated (Box 82)
    - A Great Circle, 1994-2001, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1994, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 138)
        Includes typescripts Possible titles: R. Price's Mayfield trilogy; and, four drafts of preface.
      - Proofs, 2001; 7 folders (Box 138)
        Includes proofs with Price's and Bruce Jorgasson's corrections; and, design layouts.
      - Proofs, jacket, undated (Box 110)
    - Noble Norfleet, 1997-2004, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1997-2000, 2003, undated; 8 folders (Box 138)
      - Notes and drafts, 2000-2001; 10 folders (Box 139)
        Includes typescripts with Price's revisions; and, copyediting.
      - Notes and drafts, 2001-2002, undated; 11 folders (Box 140)
      - Proofs, 2002; 2 folders (Box 140)
      - Proofs, 2001-2002, undated; 10 folders (Box 141)
        Includes jacket proofs, illustrations, and, specifications.
      - Proofs, jacket, 2002, undated (Box 110)
      - Proofs, cover, 2002 (Box 349)
      - Reviews and publicity, 2002 Jun 9-2004 Jan1 (Box 141)
      - Notes and drafts, undated; 4 Files 4 MS Word files; 1 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes drafts and chronology.
    - A Serious Way of Wondering, 2002-2006, undated
      - Notes and drafts, Peabody Lecture, 1998-2001; 2 Files 2 rtf files; 260 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      - Notes and drafts, 2002 Jun-Oct; 10 folders (Box 142)
        Includes typescripts with Price's revisions, and, Susan Moldow comments.
      - Notes and drafts, 2002 Jun 2-Jul 5, 2003-2006, undated; 4 folders (Box 143)
      - Proofs, 2003; 3 folders (Box 143)
        Includes page proofs with Price's corrections, and, ad proofs.
      - Proofs, jacket, 2003 (Box 110)
      - Proofs, cover, 2003 (Box 349)
      - Reviews, 2003 (Box 73)
      - Reviews and publicity, 2003-2004 (Box 143)
    - The Good Priest's Son, 2001-2006, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 2001 (Box 73)
        Includes articles from William to Price's on September 11 2001 attack.
      - Notes and drafts, 2002 Mar-2003 Oct, undated; 5 folders (Box 143)
        Includes notes, and typescripts with Price's revisions.
      - Notes and drafts, 2002 Mar-2004 Aug; 5 folders (Box 144)
      - Notes and drafts, 2004-2005, undated; 8 folders (Box 145)
      - Notes and drafts, 2001-2005, undated; 11 folders (Box 146)
        Includes production notes.
      - Notes and drafts, 2001, 2004, undated; 5 folders (Box 304)
      - Notes and drafts, 2004, undated; 9 folders (Box 232)
        Includes typescripts with Price's revisions.
      - Notes and drafts, proofs, 2005, undated; 9 folders (Box 233)
        Includes proofs with Price's revisions.
      - Proofs, jacket, 2005 (Box 73)
      - Proofs, cover, 2005, 2006; 2 folders (Box 349)
      - Reviews and publicity, 2005-08-14 (Box 349)
        Feature from New York Times Book Review
      - Reviews and publicity, 2005 (Box 146)
      - Reviews and publicity, 2005 (Box 73)
      - Notes and drafts, 2002-2004, undated; 31 Files 31 MS Word and text files; 6.5 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes notes on additions; chronology; dedication; Price biography; and, title page.
    - Letter to a Godchild, 2005-2006, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 2005-2006, undated; 9 folders (Box 148)
        Includes drafts with the title Dear Harper, A Letter Concerning Faith, To A Godchild.
      - Notes and drafts, undated; 3 folders (Box 305)
      - Notes and drafts, undated; 3 Files 3 MS Word file; 179 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes captions for illustrations.
      - Reviews and publicity, 2006 (Box 148)
      - Proofs, art, undated; 3 items (Box 290, Disk RL01050-CD-0005 - RL01050-CD-0007)
    - Ardent Spirits, 2000-2009, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 2000, 2009, undated; 8 folders (Box 230)
        Includes publicity documents.
      - Notes and drafts, 2005-2006; 6 folders (Box 149)
        Includes revised typescripts of book proposal.
      - Notes and drafts, 2006; 6 folders (Box 150)
      - Notes and drafts, 2006-2007, undated; 6 folders (Box 151)
      - Notes and drafts, 2007 May-Jun, undated; 9 folders (Box 152)
        Includes edits by J.C.A., and revised book proposals.
      - Notes and drafts, 2007-2008, undated; 8 folders (Box 153)
      - Notes and drafts, 2008 Jul, 2008 Oct; 7 folders (Box 154)
      - Notes and drafts, 2006, undated; 23 folders (Box 227)
      - Notes and drafts, 2005, 2007-2009, undated; 39 folders (Box 228)
        Includes edits, correspondence, production notes, and photograph captions.
      - Notes and drafts, 2008, undated; 20 folders (Box 229)
      - Notes and drafts, undated; 12 Files 12 MS Word documents; 318 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes the book proposal; notes; and, the preface.
      - Proofs, undated (Box 73)
        Includes book covers.
      - Publicity, photographs, undated (Box 320, Folder Unknown)
      - Photographs, 1955-1961, 1979, undated; 160 Files 160 jpg and tif files; 111 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
    - Midstream, 2009-2011, undated
      - Notes and drafts, undated; 2 folders (Box 155)
      - Notes and drafts, 2009-2011, undated; 5 folders (Box 306)
        Includes Susan Muldow of Scribner's notes on a pre-publication typescript.
      - Published photographic images, undated; 12 Files jpg and tif files; 234 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes dated and undated photographs and artwork published in Midstream including William and Elizabeth Price, a drawing by John Craxton, Lauritz Melchior, Leontyne Price, Michael Jordan, Rafe Jones, the Rodwell Sisters, Carroll, Samuel Barber, Stephen Spender, and Wallace Kaufman.
      - Midstream and Will Prize author photographs, Paul Whitlatch, undated; 12 Files 234 MB; jpg and tif files (Box 290, Disk RL01050-OP-0001)
    - Work for others' publications, 1989-2004, undated
      This subseries includes materials related to work Price did with other artists for their publications and is arranged chronologically.
      - The Only News, proof, 1989 (Box 102)
        Includes a galley proof of Price's introduction to Eudora Welty's Photographs.
      - Out On the Porch: An Evocation in Words and Pictures (Introduction by Reynolds Price), reviews and publicity, 1992 Jun-Jul (Box 109)
      - The Collected Stories of Truman Capote, Introduction, 2004 Sept (Box 84)
      - The Collected Stories of Truman Capote, Introduction, 2004, undated; 4 folders (Box 237)
        Includes typescripts and page proofs.
      - Bear Pond photographs, undated; 55 folders (Box 344)
        Price's poem, Gold Day, was included as the introductions to Bruce Weber's book of nude photographs.
      - Calvin Klein, Eternity, undated (Box 295, Videotape RL01050-Bcam-0004)
      - Calvin Klein, Eternity, undated (Box 298, Dvd RL01050-DVD-0019)
      - Bear Pond, electronic document, undated; 1 Files MS Word file, 3 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes note for volume.
      - The Only News, electronic document, undated; 1 Files MS Word file, 26 KB
        Includes draft of introduction to The Only News.
  - Scribner's publishing files, 1961-2013, undated
    This subseries includes files from Scribner, Price's longtime publisher. They include proposals, agreements, drafts, correspondence, reviews, and publicity and marketing materials. The materials are arranged chronologically, and by publication title.
    - A Long and Happy Life, 1961-1991; 2 folders (Box 155)
    - A Long and Happy Life, book covers, 1960 (Box 168)
    - The Connecting Imagination, 1961 (Box 350)
    - The Names and Faces of Heros, book covers, 1963 (Box 167)
    - Reynolds Price, general, 1964-1989; 4 folders (Box 155)
      Includes correspondence and photographs.
    - A Generous Man, book covers, 1966 (Box 166)
    - A Generous Man, articles and reviews, 1966-1981 (Box 167)
    - Love and Work, book covers, 1968 (Box 167)
    - Love and Work, articles and reviews, 1996 (Box 167)
    - Things Themselves, book covers, 1972 (Box 167)
    - The Optimist's Daughter, 1972 (Box 350)
      Written by Eudora Welty, galley proof.
    - Early Dark: a play - reviews, correspondence, 1962-1978 (Box 155)
    - Early Dark: a play, book covers, 1997 (Box 167)
    - Early Dark: a play, articles and reviews, 1997 (Box 168)
    - Permanent Errors, book covers, 1970 (Box 166)
    - A Palpable God, book covers, 1978 (Box 166)
    - Surface of Earth, 1975-1981 (Box 155)
    - The Surface of Earth, book covers, 1975 (Box 168)
    - The Surface of Earth, articles and reviews, 1975 (Box 169)
    - The Promise of Rest, 1975-1995 (Box 155)
    - The Source of Light, book covers, 1981 (Box 166)
    - The Source of Light, articles and reviews, 1983 (Box 168)
    - Vital Provisions, book covers, 1982 (Box 166)
    - Vital Provisions, articles and reviews, 1993 (Box 169)
    - Private Contentment, 1982-1984 (Box 155)
    - Private Contentment, book covers, 1984 (Box 167)
    - A Common Room / New Music / The Promise of Rest, 1987-1992 (Box 155)
    - New Music: A Trilogy, articles and reviews, 1989 (Box 167)
    - Kate Vaiden, 1982-1987 (Box 155)
    - Kate Vaiden, book covers, 1986 (Box 166)
    - Kate Vaiden, articles and reviews, 1986, undated; 2 folders (Box 167)
    - Kate Vaiden, publicity, 1986 (Box 169)
    - Mustian, 1982-1994; 2 folders (Box 155)
    - Mustian, book covers, 1983 (Box 167)
    - Mustian, articles and reviews, 1983 (Box 169)
    - A Common Room, 1987-1989; 6 folders (Box 155)
      Includes contract, marketing and production.
    - A Common Room, book covers, 1987 (Box 166)
    - Macmillan/A Common Room, samples, undated (Box 169)
    - A Long and Happy Life / Good Hearts, reviews, 1987-1989 (Box 156)
    - Good Hearts - reviews, sale, 1987-1988; 6 folders (Box 156)
    - Good Hearts, book covers, 1988 (Box 166)
    - Good Hearts, articles and reviews, 1988 (Box 169)
    - Good Hearts / Clear Pictures, 1987-1989 (Box 156)
    - Clear Pictures, 1987-1998; 9 folders (Box 156)
      Includes drafts, agreements, publicity, correspondence, marketing, production, and reviews.
    - Clear Pictures, 1989-1994; 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Clear Pictures, articles and reviews, 1989-1995 (Box 167)
    - Clear Pictures, book covers, 1989 (Box 168)
    - Clear Pictures, articles and reviews, 1989 (Box 168)
    - Plays / New Music / August Snow, publicity, 1989 (Box 157)
    - Night Dance, articles and reviews, 1989-1991 (Box 168)
    - Foreseeable Future, publicity, production, photographs, 1989-1992; 4 folders (Box 157)
    - The Tongues of Angels, 1989-2000; 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Use of Fire, 1990-1993; 2 folders (Box 157)
    - Blue Calhoun, 1990-2000; 4 folders (Box 157)
    - Blue Calhoun, publicity, reviews, 1992-2000; 4 folders (Box 158)
    - Blue Calhoun, book covers, 1992 (Box 166)
    - Blue Calhoun, articles and reviews, 1992 (Box 167)
    - The Blue Calhoun, publicity, 1992 (Box 169)
    - The Foreseeable Future, book covers, 1991 (Box 166)
    - A New in Life Music, The Ninth Van Cliburn International Piano Competition, 1991-1993 (Box 158)
    - Collected Stories, 1961-1992; 6 folders (Box 158)
      Includes the publishing agreement.
    - The Collected Stories, book covers, 1993 (Box 169)
    - The Collected Stories, articles and reviews, 1993-1995 (Box 167)
    - The Collected Stories, articles and reviews, 1993 (Box 168)
    - The Laws of Ice, book covers, 1986 (Box 168)
    - Roxanna Slade, 1994-1998; 5 folders (Box 158)
    - Roxana Slade, book covers, 1998 (Box 166)
    - Roxana Slade, articles and reviews, 1998 (Box 167)
    - Roxanna Slade / Ardent Spirits, 1998-2009 (Box 160)
    - The Promise of Rest, 1994-1997; 5 folders (Box 160)
    - Surface of the Earth / Source of Light / Promise of Rest, 1994-1995 (Box 160)
    - The Promise of Rest, book covers, 1995 (Box 167)
    - The Promise of Rest, articles and reviews, 1995-1996 (Box 167)
    - The Promise of Rest, publicity, 1995 (Box 169)
    - The Promise of Rest, sample pages, 1994 (Box 169)
    - Promise of Rest / Three Gospels, agreements, 1994-1995 (Box 160)
    - Three Gospels, 1994-1999; 3 folders (Box 160)
    - The Three Gospels, book covers, 1996 (Box 168)
    - The Three Gospels, articles and reviews, 1996 (Box 169)
    - Jesus of Nazareth, TIme Magazine, 1999 (Box 160)
    - A Whole New Life, 1987-1996, 2002-2004; 4 folders (Box 161)
    - A Whole New Life, book covers, 1994 (Box 166)
    - A Whole New Life, book cover, 1994 (Box 349)
    - A Whole New Life, articles and reviews, 1995 (Box 167)
    - A Whole New LIfe, articles and reviews, 1994, undated (Box 168)
    - A Whole New Life, articles and reviews, 1994-1995 (Box 169)
    - Contract history, 1994 (Box 161)
    - Bills, invoices, 1995 (Box 161)
    - Contracts, 1996-1998 (Box 161)
    - The Best of American Poetry, 1996-1998 (Box 161)
    - The Best of American Poetry 1988-1997, articles and reviews (Box 167)
    - Untitled Memoir: contracts, Gruganus, Tyler, 2009-2011 (Box 161)
    - The Collected Poems, publicity, 1997 (Box 161)
    - The Collected Poems, articles and reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 168)
    - The Collected Poems, book covers, 1997 (Box 166)
    - Letter to a Man in the Fire, includes contracts, 1998-2000; 2 folders (Box 161)
    - Letter to a Man in the Fire, book covers, 1999 (Box 169)
    - Letter to a Man in the Fire, articles and reviews, undated (Box 169)
    - Letter to a Godchild, 1999-2006 (Box 161)
    - A Perfect Friend, 1998-2002; 2 folders (Box 161)
    - Feasting the Heart, includes contracts, 2000-2002; 2 folders (Box 161)
    - Feasting the Heart, book covers, 2000 (Box 167)
    - A Great Circle, 2000-2001 (Box 161)
    - Noble Norfleet, 2001-2003; 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Noble Norfleet, articles and reviews, 2002, undated (Box 166)
    - Noble Norfleet, book covers, 2002 (Box 168)
    - A Serious Way of Wondering, 2001-2006; 3 folders (Box 162)
    - Serious Way of Wondering, marketing, 2002-2003 (Box 162)
    - Serious Way of Wondering, production, 2002-2006 (Box 162)
    - A Serious Way of Wondering, articles and reviews, 2003; 2 folders (Box 167)
    - A Serious Way of Wondering, book covers, 2003 (Box 168)
    - A Serious Way of Wondering, book cover, 2003 (Box 349)
    - Good Priest's Son, 2002-2009; 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Ardent Spirits, proposal, agreement, 2005-2009 (Box 162)
    - Ardent Spirits, articles and reviews, 2009 (Box 169)
    - Price correspondence and emails, 1985-2013; 13 folders (Box 163)
    - Articles and Reviews by Price, 1987-2009 (Box 167)
    - Biographical Articles, 1994-2008, undated (Box 167)
    - Expenses / Bills, 1991-1994 (Box 164)
    - Marketing, 1999-2003 (Box 164)
    - Pass for Press - A Common Room, 1986-1988 (Box 164)
    - Pass for Press - Good Hearts, agreement, 1987-1988 (Box 164)
    - Pass for Press - Collected Poems, 1996-1998 (Box 164)